// Target language of the test
export var metaData = {

  // Quiz flag
  flag: "/static/circle-flags/fr.svg",

  // Special characters for this test
  specialCharacters: ['é', 'à', 'è', 'ê', 'ô', 'û', 'â', 'î', 'ü', 'ù', 'ë', 'œ', 'ç', 'ï', 'É', 'À', 'È', 'Ê', 'Ô', 'Û', 'Â', 'Î', 'Ü', 'Ù', 'Ë', 'Œ', 'Ç', 'Ï'],

}



export var cards = {
  "0": {    
    type: 'text',
    question: '8 x 0 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "0"
  },
  "1": {    
    type: 'text',
    question: '8 x 1 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "8"
  },
  "2": {    
    type: 'text',
    question: '8 x 2 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "16"
  },
  "3": {    
    type: 'text',
    question: '8 x 3 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "24"
  },
  "4": {    
    type: 'text',
    question: '8 x 4 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "32"
  },
  "5": {    
    type: 'text',
    question: '8 x 5 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "40"
  },
  "6": {    
    type: 'text',
    question: '8 x 6 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "48"
  },
  "7": {    
    type: 'text',
    question: '8 x 7 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "56"
  },
  "8": {    
    type: 'text',
    question: '8 x 8 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "64"
  },
  "9": {    
    type: 'text',
    question: '8 x 9 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "72"
  },
  "10": {    
    type: 'text',
    question: '8 x 10 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "80"
  },  
};